

CONTACT

- **(a)** +55(11) 915546614
- ☑ lucas.timmy1@gmail.com
- contato.lucasazevedo1@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Estácio University Internet Systems 2020 - 2023

SKILLS

- Programming: HTML 5 (Intermediate), CSS (Intermediate), JavaScript (Intermediate), React.js (Basic), Node.js (Basic), Vite (Basic)
- Design & Tools: Tailwind CSS (Basic), Adobe Photoshop (Basic), PowerBl (Intermediate)
- Security & Infrastructure: OWASP (Basic),
 Kali Linux (Basic), Microsoft Visio (Basic),
 SharePoint (Intermediate), Active Directory
- Software Management: ServiceNow,
 Redmine (Basic), Office 365 (Intermediate)

Lucas Santos

github.com/azevedorar

ABOUT ME

Experienced in Front-end Development, Help-Desk as IT Technician, and Digital Security Analyst. I am a quick learner, especially in technology. In 2021, I interned in Help Desk at Telefônica, providing remote support using AnyDesk, TeamViewer, OCS Inventory, Redmine, Active Directory, and Microsoft Office 365. In 2022, I joined the Digital Security team at Vivo as an intern and was promoted within four months to assist the Cloud and Architecture teams. My responsibilities included security planning and risk analysis, managing ServiceNow tickets, analyzing software vulnerabilities, and supporting IT teams. During this time, I gained diverse experiences, becoming a "wild card" on the team.

LANGUAGES SKILLS

English (Intermediate), Spanish (Basic)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Vivo (Telefonica Brasil)

Information Security Analyst March 2022 - May 2024

Supported Cloud and Architecture teams in implementing the CIS Model, OWASP standards, AWS, GCP, Huawei Cloud, and Microsoft Azure. Responsibilities included:

- Collaborating with the Architecture team to research and design zero-trust security solutions.
- · Creating architectural drawings for initial security models and presenting them to various teams and management.
- Developing a Power BI-based internal wiki site for Security updates, using front-end programming skills (HTML, CSS, JavaScript) for interactivity.
- Utilizing Confluence and SharePoint for documentation and ServiceNow for ticket management involving software security analysis.

Telefonica Educação Digital

IT Help Desk Intern February 2021 - February 2022

Managed users, computers, and groups via Active Directory, handled computer maintenance with OCS Inventory, supported software installations for Office 365, and addressed employee needs through Redmine.

Phooto Brasil

IT Intern

July 2018 - December 2018

Maintained hardware and software, managed network configuration within the company.

CERTIFICATIONS

API DESIGN (API ACADEMY)

API DESIGN (API Academy) 150 hours | Completed in 2024 Cetificate Link: <u>DRIVE</u>

CyberSecurity (FIAP) 120 hours | Completed in 2023

Certificate Link: <u>DRIVE</u>

LGPD (SENAI)

4 hours | Completed in 2022 Certificate Link: <u>Senai</u>

Cloud Fundamentals, Administration, and Solution Architect (FIAP)

80 hours | Completed in 2022 Certificate Link: <u>DRIVE</u>